NADIA YNES CHAYÑA QUILLA

Mobile: (+51) 926512193 Mail: nadia.chayna.g@gmail.com

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/nadiachayna/
Portafolio: https://nadiachayna.github.io/portfolio/#contact

UX/UI designer and with studies in web programming, with experience developing projects and digital products, functional and intuitive focused on the user's needs. I'm characterized by being sociable, empathetic, perseverant, with teamwork skills, attention to detail and always willing to learn. I'm interested in learning and being part of a team, exchanging ideas, giving and receiving feedback in order to grow.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

TRASCIENDE

UI designer and content creator, September 2022 - present

- Design the web interface.
- Create content for the organization's social networks.

Achievement:

Increase new social media follower traffic and increase new volunteers at the February 2023 convocation.

MINISTERIO DEL TRABAJO Y PROMOCIÓN DEL EMPLEO

UX/UI Designer, October 2022 - March 2023

- I used the design thinking methodology for the case study research.
- I applied techniques such as benchmarking, storyboards, interviews, user persona, empathy map, journey map, information architecture, flow diagram and mvp.
- I made wireframes and prototypes for usability testing.

Achievement:

Development of the research of the project "Caserita", a mobile application, focused on providing a sales channel between merchants—customers, in order to generate income and implement financial training to merchants and make proper use of financial products that are on the market.

GLOBANT – DESIGN CENTER

UX/UI Designer, August - September 2023

- I used the design thinking methodology to research the case study and provide a solution to the problems of the company Güin Güin.
- I coordinated with the skate holder the progress of the project, as well as iterated his suggestions during the research process and layout of the application.
- Application of techniques such as benchmarking, storyboards, interviews, user persona, empathy map, journey map, information architecture, flow diagram and MVP.
- I made wireframes, prototypes for usability testing and then iterate the changes.

Achievement:

We developed the mobile application "Kushka", which focuses on improving the health of their patients and generate healthy habits through monitoring, was the result of UX research and implementation through UI design. We worked with a stakeholder in the field of functional health and was chosen by specialists through voting as the best solution.

EDUCATION

COLECTIVO 23

UX/UI Design, November 2022 - March 2023

• Specialization path as a UX/UI designer

CERTUS

UX/UI Design, October 2022 - February 2023

Graduated as UX/UI Designer

CODERHOUSE

UX/UI Design, August 2022 - February 2023

UX/UI Designer

LABORATORIA

Web programming, May 2021 - November 2021

• Front end developer

ADEX

International Business, 2016-2018

COURSES

NETZUN

August 2022

UX Best Practices.

NETZUN - UPAL

July 2022

 Specialization in Adobe Photoshop and Adobe Illustrator.

GOOGLE

April 2022

 Build Wireframes and Low-Fidelity Prototypes.

LEARNING DESIGN CENTER

March 2022

Intro to app design.

SCRUM FUNDAMENTALS CERTIFIED

March 2022

• Scrum study – Accreditation body for Scrum and agile.

GOOGLE

Febrero 2022

• Start the UX Design Process: Empathize, Define and Ideate.

GOOGLE

January 2022

• Foundations of user experience.

KNOWLEDGES

TOOLS:

Figma, Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator, Adobe XD, Marvel, Mural, Miro, Whimsical, Slack, Notion, Optimal Workshop, Canva, Github and Visual Studio Code.

PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES:

JavaScript, CSS and HTML.

LANGUAGE:

English - Level B1

RECOGNITION

WINNING TEAM OF THE SOCIAL REINVENTATHON

BANBIF, November 2022

Hackathon that aims to develop solutions with social and environmental impact, in which a solution was designed to promote the use of financial system products and use it properly.